Jury Maximau 3D Artist

Warsaw, Poland +789 803 022 3d.pivot@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a CG 3D Artist with over 20 years of experience specializing in 3D graphics and technical art. Throughout my career, I have worked on a wide range of 3D-related projects, including architectural visualizations, video production, game asset creation, and VR content for marketing and industrial presentations. My expertise extends to scripting and automating workflows to streamline 3D pipelines, enabling efficient and creative production environments.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Autodesk 3ds Max/Blender modeling, texturing, lighting, rendering, Maxscript / Python scripting, animation
- Pixyz Studio/Batch processing CAD models into game engines
- Pixologic Zbrush: Sculpturing
- Unity/Unreal/Babylon/Cesium engines
- Adobe/Substance packaes
- Other on-demand 3D tools

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

12/2018 till present - Sekai, Malta [http://www.sekai.io]

- full/part time, CAD-to-VR processing specialist
- Working out the scripted pipeline to incorporate industrial CAD models into Unreal Engine / Omniverse / Cesuim / Babylon.

3/2018 - 12/2018

- Immoviewer, Germany [http://www.immoviewer.com]
- full/part time, 3D Vusualizer/Technical Artist
- Created a scripted semi-automated pipeline to turn architectural 2D CAD or diagram plans into 3D models of apartment interiors, automatic lighting snd render setup, sending jobs to render farms, making renders for the Virtual Staging 360 tours.
- Scripting support for the pipeline
- Bespoke Arch-Viz rendering
- Creating and scripted maintaining the asset 3D objects library for Virtual Staging.

[https://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/~01296cbd65571022e3/] (User ID:Jury Maximov)

[https://sketchfab.com/j.a.m]

[https://visualisierungen.immoviewer.com/]

[https://www.buildabear.com/bear-builder-3d-workshop] (link accessible from US)

6/2008 - 3/2016

- BUZZ3D, UK [http://www.buzz3d.com, youtube.com/Buzz3DUK]
- full/part, time Lead Artist
- Created the animated 3D environments of large city areas, malls, metro/railway stations, residential
 property interiors for marketing research studies or interactive presentations, 3D models of consumer
 products, game assets.
- Animated crowd or individual human avatars. Rigged and animated vehicles, simulated vehicle traffic.
- Developed scripted tools in 3ds Max/DotNet to automate different stages of scene processing.
- Managed the outsourcing of creating 3D content and tools development.

9/2006 - 5/2008 - MONPROJECT, Belarus

- full time, Senior Artist

• Given a set of façade photos created architectural exterior/interior visualizations/renderings including low poly modeling of 6 LODs, UV mapping, creating tiled textures from photos.

9/2003 - 6/2006 - DigitalLightStudio, Belarus [http://www.dls.by]

- full time, Junior Artist

Created game models of the historical buildings.
 [3dmoscow.ru] project (a few examples on my Sketchfab page).

 Modeled, animated, and rendered the animated movie for VR amusement ride [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z3W9JBh61P0]

EDUCATION

•	MBA School of Business and Management Technology [http://www.mba.sbmt.bsu.by/en/]	2004-2006
•	Software development school Belarusian State University	1990-1993
•	Master of Arts (M.A.) Belarusian University of Culture and Fine Arts	1998-1999
•	Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Belarusian University of Culture and Fine Arts	1993-1998